[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Even the Batmobile gets hit by drunk drivers.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The popular board game Monopoly is named after the economic term of the same name which refers to what market structure?", "correct_answer": "The domination of the market by a single entity", "incorrect_answers": ["The homogenous nature of the market", "The division of the market between single (mono-) owners and joint (-poly) cooperations", "The politics of a government to encourage private property"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Dwight David Eisenhower was a great US General and the 34th President of the USA. He had thoughts of becoming a football player until he was injured tackling this great athlete.", "correct_answer": "Jim Thorpe", "incorrect_answers": ["Jim Brown", "O.J. Simpson", "Red Grange"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the winter, many turtles enter a dormant state called torpor which resembles hibernation .", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of Sir Isaac Newtons first wife?", "correct_answer": "He never had a wife", "incorrect_answers": ["Iris Barrow", "Elizabeth Rachel Sandal", "Mary Chennille"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What symbol in the movie The Da Vinci Code  was used in connection to the Holy Grail?", "correct_answer": "Chalice", "incorrect_answers": ["Fleur-de-lis", "Anhk", "Latin Cross"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He was one of the first New York graffiti vandals.", "correct_answer": "Taki 183", "incorrect_answers": ["Julio 204", "Filbo 234", "San 313"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1985 comedy-horror film features a puppet that was rejected from Ghostbusters the previous year.", "correct_answer": "Fright Night", "incorrect_answers": ["Buffy the Vampire Slayer", "The Lost Boys", "Salems Lot"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1994 Calgene introduced this genetically modified tomato cultivar which could be vine ripened without shortening the shelf life of the tomatoes.", "correct_answer": "FlavrSavr", "incorrect_answers": ["Ruby Ruth", "Oxheart", "The Hardy Jerry"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Raging Bull, Robert De Niros character loses his middleweight championship on February 14th 1951, in a fight called the St. Valentines Day Massacre. Who did he lose the championship to?", "correct_answer": "Sugar Ray Robinson", "incorrect_answers": ["Ingemarr Johannson", "Billy O Toole", "Rocky Graziano"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Box Turtles are solitary creatures who neither want nor need companions.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "George Lucas  wrote all Star Wars movies and even directed most of them.  However, this man directed Star Wars: Episode VI - Return of the Jedi.", "correct_answer": "Richard Marquand", "incorrect_answers": ["Harrison Ford", "Lawrence Kasdan", "Leigh Brackett"]}]